What about these?
Yeah, those are dope too.
Honestly.
Alright,
We'll
Take these two.
You got it.
This is for you.
Thanks for being my pack mule today!
Thanks.
All set.
Mom was a major shopaholic.
She'd shop
From dawn
Till dusk.
What else
Did she like to do
For the holidays?
It changed
Every year.
Once, we learned
Tie-dyeing in Dali.
Other times, we'd do road trips
Or paragliding.
We wanted to
See a big fireworks show...
Unfortunately...
Hey.
Let's go put these bags away.
The day's still young.
Let me
Show you some real fun.
Like what?
Keep up!
Dude,
It's freezing,
And you brought me beachcombing?
A real beachgoer doesn't care about the winter.
Well, I care. It's freezing out here.
Oh?
Still cold?
I'll believe it
When I see what you find.
Watch and learn.
Dude,
I got zero!
Don't
Give up.
It takes patience.
Keep at it!
Nothing!
I've been looking forever.
Patience.
I'll grab you a crab.
Like it's that easy!
Princess,
Your crab!
Wow! You got one!
Let me see!
Drop it in here!
We're having spicy crab tonight!
One won't cut it.
Where's the rest?
Under the big rocks.
Really?
Show-off!
You're
A natural at this.
Grandma used to
Bring me here.
Back then,
I was so jealous
Of kids
Who had their folks with them.
Once, on my birthday,
I threw a tantrum because I wanted to come.
My old man
Beat the cr*p out of me.
And then?
Grandma was furious.
She chewed him out,
And brought me here
The next day.
We stayed here until sunset.
That sounds amazing.
Best birthday
Of my life.
I wanna catch one!
Got zero so far.
I'll spot'em.
You grab'em!
Let me flip a few rocks.
I bet under here...
Oh, look!
Where?
Right here.
Ready?
Yes, yes!
Get it, quick!
I got it! I actually got it!
Where else?
I think we cleared this spot.
Let's check over here.
Try this one!
We've got a whole feast here!
They're a bit small, though.
Oh, and another one!
We're eating good tonight!
Thank you.
Thanks.
Sent!
A little gift for you.
We're closing up for the year.
There are coupons
Inside
For
Next time!
Thank you!
Happy New Year!
Enjoy the holidays.
Best wishes!
Thanks!
Travel safe!
See ya!
Alrighty!
Pork specialty coming hot!
Enjoy!
Sister!
Er...
Drop by my place
After you close, OK?
Great hand!
Show'em!
Yufen!
Keep it up.
Thanks!
Lanfang!
Take it.
See you
At my place later!
Okeydoke!
New Year, new look!
Perms for everyone!
Even me?
Grandma,
We all deserve to
Look hot!
And these cherries
Are awesome.
No wonder Qing Ye sent Kyle
To buy some when she got here.
Right?
I got the fancy ones.
The ones with...
All those letters?
Triple J!
Yes, those!
That toots
Has taste.
Even at my diner,
She only orders my signature dishes.
Hold on, Lanfang...
You paid us back,
Giving us free perms,
And buying fancy cherries?
You're not
In some kinda trouble, right?
Grandma,
What are you smiling at?
Just thinking about how good life is.
Oh yeah?
I
Am
Finally debt-free!
The salon is
Officially all mine.
No more loans,
No more stress!
Wait, shut up.
Grandma, is she serious?
100%!
We are officially outta the red.
Lanfang, oh my god!
That is amazing!
I know, right?
I literally thought
You were dying.
Scared the hell out of me!
Why would I be dying?
I've just
Been
Pinching pennies
For so long.
For once, I wanted to
Splurge!
Tell us,
What does it
Feel like?
Like I'm floating.
Like I'm
On cloud nine.
It's the
Ultimate weight
Off your shoulders.
Light at
The end of the tunnel.
Exactly that.
I hear you, babe.
I know you do.
But seriously...
Thanks for
Always
Having my back!
Oh, please.
Spare me the tears, woman!
We're practically sisters.
That's what sisters do.
Always.
You guys
Know my history.
Marrying Guodong
While pregnant...
Talk about
A
Trainwreck.
I spent so many nights crying,
Wondering why
God kept testing me.
I felt so incredibly
Hopeless.
I thought
My life was
A dead end.
But this year, it finally clicked.
Everyone is
Fighting
Their own
Battle.
If you
Get stuck,
It's a scar.
If you get through,
It's just a lesson.
Amen, sister!
You're a total badass!
The worst is behind you.
Wu is going to
Get into
A great college,
You and Grandma
Can live like queens!
D*mn straight!
I'm one foot in the grave anyway.
I just want
My babies to be happy.
Mom, shut up!
You're gonna outlive all of us!
D*mn right!
Grandma,
Take that back!
Do-over!
Unsay it!
I'll live a long, long life
And watch you all be happy!
Yay!
Much better!
Yeah!
Take a shot, win a prize!
How much?
30 a game!
C'mon!
"Sniper King?"
Why does everyone
At the shop
Call you that?
Wanna see?
Come!
Shoot to win! Give it a try!
What are we aiming for?
You tell me.
That
Baby dragon?
Please.
I want the grand prize!
The grill pan.
I want us
To have BBQ on cold nights.
It'll be cozy!
Piece of cake!
Listen to you.
Aren't we cocky today?
He's a real marksman, miss!
Hey.
Wanna play, man?
How much?
30 a round.
Prizes for
Every hit.
Clear the board,
And you take home the pan!
Sure. Let's do it.
Oorah!
Such a poser!
Watch and learn.
Wow!
Great shot, kid!
Alright,
Here's
The grand prize!
Thanks.
That was
Pure luck.
Luck?
Pick another one.
Here you go.
It's yours.
I want the
Baby dragon!
OK.
Hey,
Can I shoot two at once?
Two?
Please?
Uh, sure.
Unbelievable, man!
You're "The Sniper King," man!
Never seen anything like it!
So...
I'll take the dragon.
The baby dragon?
All yours, boss!
Still luck?
I guess not.
Now you know how I got the title.
Whatever, hotshot.
Your dragon!
Thanks.
Have a good one!
Here.
What's next?
Um...
Buddy,
Go easy on me.
Gotta make a living here.
Pretty, please...
Alright.
Thanks, man.
Bless you!
Happy New Year!
Thanks! Same to you!
So good!
Fry the lotus roots
Before we do the fish.
You got it, Mom!
Otherwise, the oil gets fishy.
Understood!
Golden brown!
To a wealthy new year!
Fortune is coming!
Mom, you're getting sweeter
By the day.
I love it.
How do these look?
Keep turning it.
G,
Does this look like your ear?
Cute, right?
Ah, so his big ears
Are made of dumplings!
Obviously!
Still too small.
Roll it out.
Hey, not bad!
This one is good.
Right?
Auntie,
Here,
Let me make one!
Add more filling.
Kiddo,
You’re doing great!
Welcome!
Ping!
I'm back.
I know.
Officer Xu told me.
You're alone?
Where's Uncle?
They went on a trip.
And you didn't join them?
Why should I?
They are family.
Fan,
It's New Year's Eve.
I got your favorites.
Let's
Have a reunion dinner.
Great!
Easy.
Here.
There you go!
Sorry,
I was so hot-headed.
I shouldn't have left you
To struggle like this.
These years...
You've had it so rough.
Stop it.
This is actually
The best New Year I've ever had.
Have a dumpling.
Look! That's beautiful!
Grandma!
My boy!
Fire in the hole!
There you go!
Whoa!
Great job, son!
Cheers! Happy New Year!
Happy New Year!
Tonight,
We celebrate
Our princess'
First New Year with us.
So
Don't hold back!
Show some love for my cooking!
Trust me, I will!
- Smells so good! - Incredible!
Here, Grandma,
Try this.
He actually won this pan
With his marksmanship!
For real?
It's my first time spending the holidays
With a real family.
I'd like to make a proper toast
To Auntie and Grandma.
Wishing you wealth,
Success,
And the best of health!
Thanks, sweetheart.
Hey, where is mine?
Uh... stay alive?
Here
Is your
Lucky money, sweetheart!
Grandma, I'm too old
For this.
You're always babies
To me!
Just take it, sweetie.
It's not much.
Take it.
Thank you, Grandma!
- That's my girl. - Wu.
Thanks, Grandma.
Love you, sweetie.
I've got yours too!
Wow, Auntie too?
Duh!
Here, son.
Score!
Princess!
Thank you, Auntie.
I got you guys gifts, too!
Alrighty,
This hand warmer is for Grandma.
Mine?
And a dress for Auntie.
Ooh, it's pink!
I love pink!
Pretty, right?
Ah, so cozy!
This blue dress
Is perfect!
Nothing for me?
Nope!
I don't buy it.
Wait,
Keep it a surprise.
Gorgeous!
Fine.
C'mon,
Time for dumplings!
Have them hot!
Right.
Let's see how mine turned out.
Here's your masterpiece.
Aww,
Thanks, Mom!
That's too pretty to be yours.
Hey! I made this one!
Nope.
Here's yours.
See? It's falling apart.
Liar!
For real.
Mom, tell her.
Ask the pot.
That's definitely yours!
It all tastes
Like happiness
Anyway.
Oh, wow!
Like it, sweetheart?
Fireworks
After dinner?
We gotta feed Tata,
Then meet the guys
For fireworks.
Got it.
Alright, kids.
Go have fun.
I should get some beauty sleep
Anyway.
Big day tomorrow!
OK, I get it!
I'll just go alone!
Enjoy your little date!
Cheers, everyone!
Happy New Year!
I'm making real cash now.
I'll send you to music school.
You'll be on prime-time TV!
Fresh dumplings!
Alright.
Make some space!
Sure, boss lady!
Dumplings and liquor, make the wallet thicker!
Babe,
Seriously...
Is this a feast
Or a
Eating contest?
It's called living in abundance!
Abundance?
This is a whole seafood market!
Yeah!
Too much!
Dig in!
Want some hard liquor?
Hell yeah!
Cool!
Pour it!
Whoa, easy!
Cheers!
Happy New Year!
Mom,
Look
What I drew!
[That's beautiful!]
She's really
Stepped up her game!
[Proud of you.]
[I know it's tough.]
[I'll make]
[your favorite pork when I'm back!]
OK!
Stay healthy, Mom!
Happy New Year!
[Happy New Year!]
Gacha games?
Buying skins?
You're
Asking for it!
You little brat!
Stay still!
Honey, chill. It's New Year's.
Spit it out!
When did you
Start playing?
Confess!
Mom!
Wait!
You little...
Dad's in this too!
Hey!
Don't you lie!
You want a
Double-team beatdown?
He spent real money!
He bought skins!
Lies!
Are you kidding me?
What even is a skin?
Listen,
You're so dead!
Happy New Year's
Beating to you!
He's lying!
He's totally addicted, Mom!
Tata!
Time for your feast!
Is he not around?
Open it.
He'll
Smell the food.
Tata!
Come on, Tata!
Come
And eat!
Oh, there he is!
Come on!
Hey, boy.
Here you go.
Is she your girlfriend?
Aren't you a little ladies' man?
Happy New Year, sweeties.
Happy New Year.
Look at those
Lotus lanterns!
Beautiful!
Happy New Year!
Best wishes!
Same to you!
Happy New Year!
Cold?
A little.
Time is just flying by.
Here, warm up.
It's already
Been half a...
Watch out!
My bad! You hurt?
No, I'm good.
I'm OK.
Let it cool down a bit.
These past months went so fast.
Even Tata is all grown up.
My past
Feels like
It happened in another life.
Disappointed
You're not in Beijing?
Honestly, Beijing lacks this vibe.
With Dad away,
Mom and I
Just ate
And watched TV.
But here,
It's so cozy.
It feels like home.
Back home,
We barely spoke.
We just
Spent the night networking,
Responding to
Endless texts.
I don't even remember
What the dinners
Tasted like.
And tonight?
With
Everything happened with Dad,
It's pretty quiet.
Only Mr. Sun
Sent me some money.
But celebrating
With you guys...
I actually felt like
Part of a family.
I even know
What the filling was!
I felt so involved!
Please,
You ate way more than you made.
Yours
Turned into mush!
I had to choke it down.
Hey,
At least they were soft!
Saved you some chewing!
My jaw sends its regards.
You're welcome, big guy.
No more?
It's Meng Ruihang.
Take it.
[Qing Ye,]
[Happy New Year!]
[How's the countryside treating you?]
[Pretty good.]
[Nice.]
[You guys should]
[come over]
[and hang out sometime.]
He's right here!
Happy New Year.
[Happy New Year!]
Happy New Year!
Gotta go!
Come here.
Cold?
Not anymore.
Let's go.
Xing Wu...
Yeah?
Can we
Do this again next year?
Where
Will you be next year?
Depends on
How I do on my college exams....
But I really
Wanna be here.
You've always
Had a clear path
Ahead.
Just keep moving forward.
Oh, I will.
I'm going to
Crush it.
There you are!
Been looking forever.
Time for fireworks!
That's a lot!
Pick one.
Lanfang,
You bought all these?
Must've cost a fortune!
You guys always buy.
My treat this time!
Go wild!
Look at you!
We're not gonna say no!
- Hell yeah! - Grab'em.
Party!
C'mon,
One more!
Really?
You OK?
Easy peasy!
Watch your back, tough guy!
Hey,
I'm in my prime!
Grab it.
Careful!
Jeez...
Off we go!
Over here.
Here works.
Go, go, go!
Watch out!
Easy!
Watch it, man!
Beautiful!
Yay!
Fun?
Totally!
It spits fire!
This is awesome!
Happy New Year!
[Happy New Year, man!]
[Happy New Year!]
[Stay healthy!]
[Wishing you the best!]
So lively.
Shi Min,
Happy New Year!
[Happy New Year!]
It sounds crazy there!
Fireworks?
Yep,
Check this out!
Oh, wow!
Guys!
Almost midnight!
Countdown time!
Happy New Year!
Big bucks coming!
Happy New Year.
Lanfang,
Make a wish!
For the coming days!
Yeah! Wish! Wish!
Do it!
I hope we all
Stay happy,
Life keeps getting better,
And my salon does great!
Stunning!
Happy New Year!
Happy... Wait, stop!
Lanfang,
Your house is burning!
Your house is on fire!
Oh my god, fire!
A firework must have hit it!
Move!
Oh god!
Fire!
What happened?
Hey...
Don't freeze! Get water!
What do we do?
Mom is still in there...
Lord...
Hey?
Wu!
Come back!
[The house is on fire!]
Let's go!
The salon is on fire!
Mom is inside! God...
Lanfang,
Don't!
Mom!
Lanfang,
Stay back!
Mom!
Mom...
Xingfu Third Street!
Xuan Island!
Please hurry!
Where's Mom?
Wu!
- She's inside! - Auntie...
Auntie!
Mom!
Lanfang, are you crazy!
Calm down!
Grandma is still in there!
Your grandma...
Grandma...
Wu! No!
Wu!
Xing Wu!
Son!
Mom!
How did this happen?
Fire...
Do something!
Xing Wu went in!
Get some water!
Come on!
Grandma!
Help! Help!
Fire!
Grandma!
Sweetie, help!
Wu!
I'm here.
Be careful, Kyle!
Watch out, son!
Xing Wu!
Oh god...
They'll be OK.
I've got you.
I'm here, Grandma!
OK.
Get on my back.
Come on!
OK...
They'll make it...
Auntie...
I've got you!
Hold tight, Grandma!
OK...
Let's go.
Fire trucks!
Over here!
Back up!
All of you, back!
Watch out!
Chemicals inside!
Toxic fumes!
Step back!
Clear the area!
They're trapped inside!
My boy is in there!
My mom too!
Please!
Move! Go to the back!
Wu! What now?
Hold tight,
Grandma!
Just hold on!
Watch it,
Sweetie.
Mom!
Lanfang...
Xing Wu!
Dude, you're fine!
Mom!
Wu...
- I'm fine. - Grandma...
Check Grandma.
You OK?
Do we need an ambulance?
That was too close...
I'm OK!
I'm fine...
Fine...
Qing Ye,
Your laptop...
C'mon,
Let's go to my place.
OK.
Move, move.
Go.
Easy, easy.
Watch your step!
Easy.
It's over,
Grandma.
I'm here.
Don worry.
The salon is gone,
But we're all here.
Grandma,
Cold?
Take my jacket.
Wear mine.
Yours is soaked.
OK.
I'm fine, really.
It's OK, Mom...
We're safe now.
Grandma, here.
It's over...
Put this on.
Get some water
In you.
Grandma, drink.
You first.
Please, just drink!
You're safe now.
Here, Wu.
Thanks,
Appreciate it.
Wu...
Your wrist...
Oh my god, Xing Wu...
You're hurt...
I'm fine,
Really.
We
Slipped out
The back yard.
Lucky her room had a back door,
Or we'd be
In real trouble.
Thank god...
Yeah. Thank god.
Grandma,
Thank god!
We're all here.
How is it?
It's under control.
Chemical hazard inside.
Stay out.
We'll keep you updated.
OK.
Thank you.
Thank you so much!
The fire is out.
Grandma.
It's all good.
Lanfang,
You're staying with me tonight.
Big G
Is setting up the room.
And the kids are staying with me!
Wu,
Did Kyle tell you?
Yeah.
Good.
We have plenty of space.
Got everything
Ready.
I kicked my husband out
To a buddy's
So you guys
Could have more space.
Thanks.
Thanks for taking care of Mom and Grandma.
We won't stay long.
Come on!
That's what neighbors
Are for!
Lanfang, relax.
We are right here with you.
It's alright, Grandma.
Thank you, everyone.
No problem.
Auntie,
You and Grandma
Get some rest.
We'll deal with
Everything tomorrow.
Yeah.
She's right.
Crash here,
Guys.
Make yourselves
At home.
Oh,
Mom put some toiletries together.
Just holler if you need anything.
Thanks,
Bro.
I'll head down.
OK.
Towels,
Toiletries,
Slippers...
Everything is new.
You're in that room tonight.
Bathroom is by the stairs.
Hot water is ready.
Left is hot,
Right is cold.
Yufen
Packed some clothes.
I'll bring them up later.
Anything else...
Thank you.
OK.
Here.
Just relax tonight.
Take a hot shower
And rest.
I'll go wash up.
Here, Mom.
OK.
Good temp?
Relax.
Grandma,
Brought a quilt
For the cold.
I'll redo
The bedsheets in a second.
Thanks for everything!
Come on.
Make yourself at home.
My husband and son are staying
At my dad's.
C'mon, I'll do it.
Nah,
Seriously,
Stay with Grandma!
You guys have helped enough.
Get some rest.
It's fine.
You're exhausted.
Stay with Grandma.
Two pairs of hands
Are faster!
Come on,
Let's go.
I'll lend a hand.
Here, Mom.
It's cool.
Let them help.
OK.
Lift your chin.
[Hello,]
[the line is busy...]
[Mom, how is Grandma?]
[We should]
[get her checked]
[tomorrow.]
Qing Ye?
Come in.
Brought you this.
Thanks.
It's Kyle's charger.
See
If the laptop works.
It was a life-and-death moment.
Why did you save my laptop?
It's important,
Right?
You are way more important!
Just try it.
Your hand is blistered.
It's fine.
Don't worry.
You need burn cream.
I'll go get some...
Trust me,
I'm fine.
I heal fast.
Get some rest.
Xing Wu...
Are you sure you're OK?
Seriously,
I'm fine.
I'll just put some ice pops
On it.
It'll soothe the burn.